hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装弹簧提示
week's installment we're gonna take a
一周的分期付款
look at something that's just been
看看刚刚发生的事情
released a brand new thing that we just
发布了一个全新的东西，我们只是
announced in the last few days on the
最近几天在
good old-fashioned spring IO blog the
好的老式IO博客
trustworthy venerable spring L blog that
值得信赖的尊敬的春天L博客
is namely the new support in spring
是春季的新支撑
match for Kafka right mom would been
匹配卡夫卡对的妈妈会
haseen one of the legendary spring batch
haseen传说中的春季批次之一
team members just announced this and I
团队成员刚刚宣布了这一点，而我
guess the large chunk of the
猜猜大块的
contribution came from the community by
贡献来自社区
a Matthew Calais I'm gonna go ahead and
我要去的Matthew Calais
guess but oh no oh oh hey wiener I don't
猜猜，但哦，不，哦，哦，维也纳，我不
know I'm sure it's French and I should
知道我确定是法国人，我应该
know how to pronounce it but I I don't
知道如何发音，但II不
know either way merci thank you so the
知道哪种方式谢谢你，所以
point is we have this nice new support
关键是我们有了这个不错的新支持
in spring match for working with Kafka
在春季比赛中与Kafka合作
and I just came back from Brazil I was
我刚从巴西回来时
in Brazil let's say you know seven
在巴西，假设您知道七个
four or five days ago it's now Wednesday
四五天前，现在是星期三
right as this goes up and I was in
就在这上升的时候，我在
Brazil just a few less than a week ago
巴西不到一个星期前
okay let's say it's a week ago and when
好吧，让我们说这是一个星期前
I was in Brazil I talked to a large
我在巴西和很多人聊天
Brazilian bank and they're using spring
巴西银行，他们正在使用春季
batch they're starting new projects and
批处理他们正在开始新项目，
spring batch now I love streaming
我现在喜欢流媒体春季批
processing I love messaging I love
处理我爱的消息我爱
integration I love all these things that
整合我喜欢所有这些东西
have to do with sort of streaming
与某种流有关
workloads and moving data through
工作负载和数据移动
processing pipelines but at the end of
处理管道，但在末尾
the day there are some things that just
那天有一些事情
lend themselves naturally to batch and I
自然地将它们借给我
think a question that a lot of people
想到一个很多人的问题
struggle with is how do I bridge these
奋斗是我如何弥合这些
two universes I've got things that are
我有两个宇宙
naturally finite they are time boxed
天生有限，他们有时间限制
they are windowed they are whatever we
他们开着窗户，无论我们做什么
need to whatever you know you need to
需要你所知道的一切
whatever you need to understand to make
您需要了解的任何东西
to understand that they are limited
了解他们是有限的
right there might be something that gets
可能有一些东西
processed and there's report that gets
已处理，并且有报告
sent out for management there's a some
派人去管理
sort of analytics that are done whatever
可以完成任何类型的分析
right and so this is a very common thing
对，所以这是很常见的事情
is how do I
我该怎么办
take my streaming processing pipelines
带我的流处理管道
these things that are producing data all
这些正在产生数据的东西
the time based on their online sort of
根据他们在线上的时间
transactional world that we live in and
我们生活的交易世界
how do I turn that into data well one
我该如何将其转化为数据
way to do that of course is to is to
要做的当然是
forward it on to on to spring batch now
现在将其转发到春季批处理
spring batch is great because it can
春天批次很棒，因为它可以
process large amounts of data and spring
处理大量数据并弹跳
batch has a lot of stuff built in that
批处理中内置了很多东西
just makes life easier a lot of stuff
只是让生活变得轻松很多
that I think most people don't really
我认为大多数人不是真的
appreciate until they kind of take for
欣赏，直到他们喜欢
granted what a spring batch can do but
授予春季批可以做什么，但
for example spring batch runs in the
例如春季批处理在
background and it has a database of
背景，它有一个数据库
metadata system and that's metadata
元数据系统，那就是元数据
system is is stored somewhere namely in
系统存储在某个地方
a job repository which interns in by
一个由
default stores it in the sequel data
默认将其存储在续集数据中
store the benefit of this is that a
存储的好处是
spring batch job which in terms of its
春季批处理工作
domain model anyway is a job composed of
无论如何，领域模型是一项工作，由
multiple steps each of which describes
多个步骤，每个步骤描述
how to read and then write and
如何阅读然后写作以及
optionally process data write a job has
可选地，处理写入作业的数据
it has metadata about the state of that
它具有有关该状态的元数据
job of the execution of that job
执行该工作的工作
persisted in the database so if
保留在数据库中，所以如果
something should go wrong as this want
想要的东西应该出问题了
to happen when you work in the real
当你在现实中工作时发生
world right there's gonna be data that
正确的世界将会有数据
sometimes got an a failure of encoding
有时编码失败
or something like that right I saw I
或类似的东西，我看到我
think Holden Corral just tweeted or
认为Holden Corral刚刚发了推文，或者
retweeted or something she observe the
转推或她观察到的内容
tweet or you know Oh Age 2 tweeters I
或您知道哦，年龄2高音我
don't know something she just tweeted
不知道她刚刚发过推文
something that I thought was really
我以为是真的
funny which is um if all of our JSON if
有趣的是，如果我们所有的JSON都为um
we required a schema for all of our JSON
我们需要所有JSON的架构
again I'm paraphrasing here but if we
我再次在这里释义，但如果我们
required a JSON file a schema file for
需要一个JSON文件和一个架构文件
all of our jason then we wouldn't have
我们所有的杰森，然后我们就不会
any data basically
基本上任何数据
I don't know I have no idea what that
我不知道那是什么
was I can play I meant I may have very
我可以玩我的意思是我可能有
well took it out of context it made me
好让它脱离了上下文，这让我
laugh though because it's true right
虽然笑，因为这是对的
there's there's just this huge sort of
有一种巨大的
world of data out there and we need to
数据的世界，我们需要
make do with what we can write and and
尽我们所能写的，以及
that's how the large majority of I think
我就是这么认为的
work has done these days
这些天工作已经完成
it's just normalizing that guy stuff
只是规范那个家伙的东西
right so what are we gonna do we want to
对，所以我们要做什么
take data from the real world we want to
从我们想要的现实世界中获取数据
take it from the road and process it the
从路上拿走并处理它
easiest way I can think of doing that is
我想到的最简单的方法是
the spring batch spring baptize this
春天批春施洗
metadata system if something goes wrong
元数据系统出现问题
as it will if you have invalid or on you
如果您有病或在您身上无效
know invalid as a formatted data you can
知道无效的格式化数据可以
as an operator intervene in the job and
作为操作员干预工作，
restart it
重新启动
you can also provide heuristics you can
您还可以提供启发式
say okay well if I fail you know some
如果我失败，可以说很好，你知道一些
percent of the data or some number of
数据的百分比或一定数量的
records of the data then go ahead and
数据记录然后继续
fail the whole job but if it's just a
整个工作都失败了，但如果仅仅是
small you know if it's a subset of the
小，你知道它是否是
data then you know don't bother right
数据，那么你就知道不用打扰了
don't don't bother failing it just keep
不要为失败而烦恼
going just ignore those records it works
只是忽略那些有效的记录
in chunks so you have this idea of a of
大块的所以你有一个
steps and steps process they read data
步骤和步骤处理他们读取数据
in chunks maybe you know X number of
也许你知道X的数量
Records where X is whatever size
记录X的大小
boundary you can afford to both store in
您可以负担得起的边界
memory at the same time and and lose
记忆在同一时间和失去
possibly right because if you lose one
可能正确，因为如果您输了一个
record in the chunk then the whole chunk
记录在块中，然后记录整个块
it could possibly be lost so chunks are
它可能会丢失，所以块是
and it's also a unit of performance you
这也是你的表现单位
know how many records do I want to write
知道我要写多少条记录
to the downstream thing in a transaction
到交易中的下游事物
now logical transaction if not an actual
现在逻辑交易，如果不是实际的
transaction right that's called a chunk
所谓的交易权
so you know I don't want to review all
所以你知道我不想复习所有
of spring batch again we've done
我们已经完成了春季批处理
actually one of the earlier spring tips
实际上是较早的春季技巧之一
videos I did one of the more popular
我做过比较受欢迎的影片之一
ones indeed was a spring tip that just
确实是一个春天的提示，
looked at spring batch 101 right spring
看着春天的101批春
back to basics 101 what I think is
回到基础101我认为是
interesting here is this possibility of
有趣的是这种可能性
bridging batch with messaging through
通过消息将批处理桥接
the use of this new Kafka support so
使用这个新的Kafka支持
that's we're gonna do today friends
那就是我们今天要做的朋友
we're gonna take a look at this really
我们要看看这个
really cool stuff we can get at it from
我们可以从中获得非常酷的东西
the spring initializer of course we can
春天的初始化器，我们当然可以
build new projects as usual and this
像往常一样建立新项目
will be this is already available this
将是这个已经可用了吗
this Kafka support is gonna be available
该Kafka支持将可用
in spring boot 2.2 m3 when that comes
在 spring boot 2.2立方米的时候
out and in the meantime it's available
出去，与此同时它可用
in the snapshot stuff right so it's a
在快照中，所以它是一个
spring back for that 200 m2 and I'm
回去那200平方米，我
going to be using spring boot to tattoo
将要使用弹簧靴纹身
Oh snapshot which intern
哦，快照哪个实习生
pulls in spring batch 4.20 m2 okay so
拉入弹簧批4.20平方米好
I'm just gonna call this BK batch Kafka
我只是叫这批BK卡夫卡
okay and we're gonna bring in the Kafka
好吧，我们要带卡夫卡
dependencies and the spring batch
依赖和Spring批处理
dependencies and h2 now again we're not
依赖和h2现在我们又不是
doing anything with JDBC here but spring
除了春天，在这里用JDBC做任何事情
batch needs to persist its metadata
批处理需要保留其元数据
somewhere I'll give it an in-memory data
在某处我会给它一个内存数据
store you can put you can point this to
你可以把它指向的商店
really any modern sort of sequel JDBC
几乎任何现代的续集JDBC
data store and it'll do the right thing
数据存储，它将做正确的事
but I just want the fast recite restart
但我只想快速重新朗诵
cycle so let's go ahead and generate a
循环，所以让我们继续并生成一个
project here we are open this up
我们在这里打开这个项目
all righty
好吧
so we need to configure a few things I
所以我们需要配置一些东西
want to get that out of the way first
想要先解决这个问题
because it's early enough and you know
因为还早，你知道
it's early enough for the project that I
对于这个项目，我还早
might be able to remember it but if I
也许可以记住它，但是如果我
put it yet I might get I might
把它，但我可能会得到我可能
experience odd errors later on so we
后来遇到奇怪的错误，所以我们
need several things and these are just
需要几件事，这些只是
regular spring boot and spring for Kafka
常规弹簧靴和卡夫卡弹簧
support properties right there's nothing
支持属性就没有了
special here
特别在这里
so we want consumer properties okay so
所以我们希望消费者财产可以
we're gonna propagate we're gonna work
我们要传播我们要工作
with data here first of all in our code
首先在我们的代码中添加数据
we don't create an entity or an object
我们不创建实体或对象
or a detail called guess what customer
或称为猜测客户的详细信息
get rid of that all right so customer
摆脱所有的问题，这样客户
that's gonna be our thing and the
那将是我们的事，
customer is gonna have a field here will
客户将在这里有一个领域
have an ID and will have a field called
有一个ID，并将有一个名为
string name and you know what I think I
字符串名称，您知道我的想法
forgot to bring in a game I forgot to
忘了带上我忘了的游戏
bring in Lombok so I'll go ahead and
带上龙目岛，所以我会继续
just add this manually I'll use Java
只需手动添加即可，我将使用Java
Levin I should have done that I should
莱文我应该做的我应该做的
have done both of those things back at
已经在
the initializer but thankfully this is
初始化器，但幸运的是，这是
just trivial even in the bill because
即使在账单中也只是微不足道的，因为
all the do dependencies are managed for
所有的do依赖项都被管理
us so I don't really pay a lot of I
我们，所以我并没有付出很多
don't read there's no not a huge cost
不读，没有不菲的代价
and complexity here as long as I know
我知道这里的复杂性
the goop ID and the artifact the
goop ID和工件
versions and all the exclusions and all
版本，所有排除项目和所有
that stuff is already mandatory by
这些东西已经是强制性的了
spring boot okay so what do we do we're
春天的靴子好吧，那我们该怎么办
gonna have a consumer and you can see
会有一个消费者，你可以看到
our entity it's going to use you know
我们的实体将使用您知道
all the things that Lombok gives us so
龙目岛给我们的所有东西
generate a constructor a some setters
生成一些构造函数的构造函数
and you know to string equals hash code
而且你知道字符串等于哈希码
blah blah blah and now that we know that
等等等等，现在我们知道了
we need to because it's Kafka we need to
我们需要，因为它是卡夫卡，我们需要
specify a key D serializer
指定密钥D序列化器
all right and I I want to use long
好吧，我想用久
deserialize ER because our our ID get
反序列化ER，因为我们的ID已获得
along right so here's this
沿着右边，这是这里
and again again like I should I could
一遍又一遍我应该
and should probably do a whole video on
并且可能应该在
just Kafka in spring and I've done
只是卡夫卡在春天，我已经完成了
something you've seen me talk about
你看过我的话题
spring cloud stream they'd seen me talk
春天的云流他们见过我说话
about um spring code stream Kafka
关于um​​ spring代码流Kafka
streams in particular spring cloud
溪流特别是春云
stream works with RabbitMQ or Kafka or
流适用于RabbitMQ或Kafka或
ABS you know Amazon Kinesis or Google
您知道Amazon Kinesis或Google的ABS
cloud pub/sub or whatever but it just as
云发布/订阅或其他任何东西，但是就像
easily works with spring cloud stream
轻松与Spring Cloud Stream一起使用
and Kafka but I've also done want one on
和卡夫卡，但我也确实想要一个
spring cloud stream Kafka streams which
春季云流卡夫卡流
is interesting um okay okay good
很有趣嗯好的好的
we've got that now I want the value
现在我们想要的是价值
deserialize er so I'm gonna say without
反序列化，所以我要说不
you you see later
你以后你会看到
make sure don't misspell it twice and
确保不要误拼两次
I'm going to use the JSON deserialize er
我将使用JSON反序列化器
all right that's for me a spring project
对我来说这是一个春季项目
here not this one
这里不是这个
there you go okay so I've got this copy
那里你还好，所以我有这个副本
reference okay
参考还可以
um when we give it a goop ID and
嗯，当我们给它一个树冠ID和
actually so I'm gonna call this
实际上，所以我要称呼它
customers group good and producer will
客户群商品，生产者将
be he serialize won't be a long
是他序列化不会很长
sterilizer so I'll look up the long
消毒器，所以我会很长一段时间
sterilizer as well same idea right I
消毒器以及同样的想法我
just want to have a thing that will
只是想拥有一件会
handle the persistence of the key in
处理密钥的持久性
Kafka in coffee but this concept of a
卡夫卡咖啡，但这种概念
message and messages have keys and then
消息和消息具有密钥，然后
a body and the body is the value and now
身体，身体就是价值，现在
the reason that you have this this
你有这个的原因
concept of a key is because of the fact
钥匙的概念是因为事实
that really you're not dealing with a
真的，你不是在和一个
message queue what you're dealing with
消息队列您正在处理的内容
is an append-only log it's a data store
是仅追加日志，是数据存储
and so this makes it possible for you to
因此，这使您可以
use spring cloud stream cough with
用春云流咳
streams to do some very interesting
流做一些很有趣的事情
things that that treat cough cough like
治咳嗽之类的东西
a database right and
数据库权限和
Effects of that is that you have to
效果是您必须
think about well keys basically which is
基本上考虑好钥匙
fine not a big deal we can handle this
没什么大不了的，我们可以处理
don't know if we could handle much more
不知道我们能否应付更多
but looking to me handle this right all
但期待我能正确处理
right
对
there's the s your laser and we want the
有你的激光，我们想要
client ID why is that right please yes
客户ID为什么是这样，请是
okay and one thing that's gonna be an
好吧，一件事将是
issue is it's gonna ask us to we're
问题是它会问我们
decode data we're gonna though we're
解码我们要的数据
gonna write two programs and they're
要写两个程序，他们
gonna send data from one node to another
将数据从一个节点发送到另一个
we're gonna transit through Kafka and on
我们要经过卡夫卡等等
the other as data pops out on the other
另一个因为数据突然弹出
side we have to DC a lot deserialize it
方面，我们必须将其反序列化很多
and we're gonna do so using jackson
我们将使用杰克逊
which by default doesn't just
默认情况下不只是
deserialize arbitrary object you have to
反序列化任意对象
tell it to relax basically and the way
告诉它基本放松和方式
you do that is with a trusted package so
您使用受信任的程序包来执行此操作
kafka consumer properties is a spring
卡夫卡的消费属性是春天
json trusted packages equals asterisk
json受信任的软件包等于星号
packages packages all right good and
打包好的包装
finally we're gonna be sending messages
终于我们要发送信息了
to the Kafka topic topic as the it's the
到Kafka主题，因为它是
way that they say cue you need Kafka all
他们说提示你需要全部卡夫卡的方式
right and we want to specify the default
正确，我们要指定默认值
one for the Kafka template okay so
一个卡夫卡模板好吧
that's everything that's common to both
这是双方共同的一切
producer and consumer
生产者和消费者
let's now break the examples down so
现在让我们分解这些例子
we're gonna create a producer
我们将创建一个生产者
application which is gonna be a spring
春天的应用
batch application that just leads from
批处理应用程序只是从
well actually I'm gonna synthesize some
好吧，实际上我要合成一些
data it's just gonna be a thing that's
数据只会是一件事情
just gonna pump data into Kafka and then
只是将数据注入Kafka，然后
something else will come along on the
会有其他事情发生
reader side and read the data off the
读取器端读取数据
queue and write it to something else now
排队并将其写入其他内容
I don't want to actually get into the
我不想真正进入
business of configuring you know file
配置您知道文件的业务
inbound you know file item readers and
入站，您知道文件项读取器，并且
or flat file item readers and Mongo item
或平面文件项目阅读器和Mongo项目
writers and that kind of stuff so I'm
作家之类的东西，所以我
just gonna for the things that don't
只是为了那些没有的东西
have to do with Kafka the things that
与卡夫卡有关
are the you know the invariants in our
您是否知道我们的不变式
demo I'm just gonna provide dummy
演示，我只是提供假人
implementations of the interface as
接口的实现为
expected and we're gonna look mainly at
预期，我们将主要关注
what happens with the Kafka so producer
卡夫卡制作人怎么办
application this is gonna be the thing
应用程序这将是事情
that we'll just pump data into a Kafka
我们将数据泵入Kafka
broker it's gonna be a spring batch
经纪人，这将是一个春季批
application and the first thing you have
应用程序和您拥有的第一件事
to do of course besides installing
当然要安装
something batch besides making swing
除了摇摆之外还有些东西
batch and spring boot rather work so
批处理和春季引导宁可如此工作
let's do that let's get that other way
让我们做到这一点，让我们得到另一种方式
okay we got this now we've got that now
好吧，我们现在有了这个，我们现在有了
so this spring application got run okay
所以这个春天的应用程序运行正常
all right there is this now it's a
好吧，现在有一个
spring badge application we need to tell
我们需要告诉的春季徽章申请
spring boot to go ahead and create a
春天的靴子继续前进，并创建一个
spring batch job repository and launcher
春季批作业存储库和启动器
and all that stuff and in order for that
和所有的东西，为了
to happen we need to say at enable batch
发生，我们需要在启用批量时说
processing and that's the hard part
处理，这是困难的部分
right that's most of what we have to do
对，这是我们要做的大部分事情
to get spring batch working the only
使春季批工作唯一
thing then is we need to provide a
然后，我们需要提供一个
definition of a job and a job needs to
工作的定义和工作需要
have a some steps and you know all that
有一些步骤，你知道的一切
kind of stuff so we're gonna we're gonna
东西，所以我们要
create a writer that's gonna read data
创建一个将读取数据的作家
from this arbitrary just in variant
从这个任意的只是变种
dummy reader okay so we wouldn't want we
虚拟读者好吧，所以我们不想我们
want a beam that has a job okay and in
想要一个可以正常工作的光束
order to create the beam we're going to
为了创建光束，我们要
inject a few things that we need the
注入一些我们需要的东西
least of which is a job builder Factory
至少其中一个是工作建设者工厂
okay and a step above the factory so I
好吧，离工厂又一步了，所以我
tend to just bring these in for every
倾向于将这些带入每个
spring batch app I build these days
这些天我构建的春季批处理应用程序
they're just help and I'm gonna inject
他们只是帮忙，我要注入
these into the constructor inside my
这些进入我的构造函数里面
main application this is my
这是我的主要应用
configuration class we're just gonna
我们将要使用的配置类
inject them in the constructor but
将它们注入构造函数中，但是
rather than write the constructor by
而不是写构造函数
hand I'll use required arcs constructor
我将使用必需的圆弧构造函数
and we'll just do that okay so this dot
我们会做的很好，所以这个点
job build a factory dot get jobs I don't
工作建立一个工厂点得到我没有的工作
know whatever job let me give it no
知道什么工作让我不给
that's not good job job please
那不是好工作
job but QuickTime just really drags this
工作，但QuickTime确实拖了这个
computer down okay um and then further
电脑掉下来好吧，然后进一步
we're gonna have a step we'll come back
我们要走一步，我们会回来
to that definition in just a moment so
很快就达到了这个定义
step good come back to you
一步好回到你身边
but start is this step okay and we'd
但是开始是可以的，我们会
have an increment er a new one ID
增加一个新的一个ID
incrementer just create a new unique ID
增量器只需创建一个新的唯一ID
for the job itself so that if I need to
工作本身，所以如果我需要
point to a particular one and say we
指向一个特定的人说我们
start that one I have a that's that's
开始那个我有一个就是那个
the parameter that'll make this job
可以完成这项工作的参数
implication unique okay good so we've
含义独特，很好，所以我们已经
got now just a basic job with one step
现在只需一步就可以完成基本工作
and as I said before the steps have you
正如我在步骤之前所说的那样
know three things readers writers and
了解读者作家的三件事
processors so our step will be it'll be
处理器，所以我们要做的就是
a thing that uses the step build a
使用步骤构建的东西
factory - you know that's one and then
工厂-你知道那是一个
that one turn chunk let's say ten
那一转大块说十
records at a time and in order to do
一次记录并为了
that we're going to read and write data
我们将要读写数据
type of customer okay
客户类型还可以
don't even put that from our DTL and
甚至不要从我们的DTL和
we're going to read data so we'll come
我们将要读取数据，所以我们来
back to this in a second but suffice it
回到一秒钟，但足够了
to say it's gonna be a very invariant
说这将是一个非常不变的
thing so leader equals new item leader
所以领导者等于新项目领导者
nothing fancy here I entities a type
没什么特别的，我在这里实体类型
customer okay
顾客还可以
read that in okay so there's a little
读，没关系，所以有一点
reader we'll come back to that in a
读者，我们将在
second and the writer and the item
其次是作家和作品
writer what I want to do is I want to
作家我想做的是
use Kafka right so this is where the
用卡夫卡吧，所以这是
rubber meets the road here that'll be a
橡胶遇上了这条路
separate beam and we'll just say at beam
分开的光束，我们只说一声
Kafka item writer managing entity the
卡夫卡项目作家管理实体
lip type long key peplum of type
唇型长按键型
customer
顾客
Kafka item mayor okay okay and we're
Kafka项目市长好吧好吧，我们
gonna come back to that in a second okay
再过一遍再说
all right so there's our basic thing
好吧，这是我们的基本要求
we're going to use a builder here don't
我们将在这里使用一个生成器
have to do a lot of work to get that to
必须做很多工作才能做到这一点
work Kafka item writer dot want the
工作卡夫卡项目作家点想要
builder dummy so cough kind of writer
建设者假人这么咳嗽的作家
builder build Kafka template will inject
构建器构建Kafka模板将注入
the Kafka template privatized in the
Kafka模板在
same way and again spring boots gonna
同样的方式弹簧靴会
automatically configure that that object
自动配置该对象
for us based on the the auto
对我们来说基于汽车
configuration so we really need to get
配置，所以我们真的需要获取
that
那
and well we've already got it I think we
好吧，我们已经有了它，我想我们
already injected into the code didn't we
已经注入了代码，不是吗
know it should okay I'll just inject it
知道应该没问题，我将其注入
here rather than sunny thickens the the
这里而不是晴天会使
parameter list there why not I'll
参数列表在那里，我为什么不
probably use this again there we go
大概再用一次
it's complaining that it hasn't it can't
它抱怨它不是，它不能
find it by type but that's IntelliJ
按类型查找它，但这是IntelliJ
stooling not the actual sort of state of
踩踏而不是实际的状态
the world what else I need to tell it
这个世界我还有什么要说的
how to take a object and turn it into a
如何把一个物体变成一个
thing that it can send in order to do
它可以发送以执行的操作
that and you just have a key so I'm
那，你只有一把钥匙，所以我
going to tell it how to convert a
告诉它如何转换
customer into a key in the customer is a
客户成为客户的关键
if the object that we're taking right so
如果我们正确的对象是
a new customer
新客户
okay so convertor from customers long
好吧，所以客户的转换器很久了
there you go Kafka item writer the key
你去那里卡夫卡项目作家的钥匙
and then value okay alright good so
然后值好吧好吧所以
customer dot get ID all right
客户点获取ID正确
seems easy enough right I think I could
似乎很简单，我想我可以
I think I can do this
我想我能做到
that should work we've got the topic
应该可行，我们已经有了主题
topic specified so the only thing we
指定主题，所以我们唯一要做的就是
need now is our reader is that true I
现在需要的是我们的读者是真的我
think that's fair
认为这很公平
item right
公鸡项目对
and finally our reader now the reader
最后是我们的读者现在是读者
all this thing's gonna do is gonna
这件事要做的就是
create a new unique ID using an atomic
使用原子创建一个新的唯一ID
long okay it's just dummy data you can
好吧，这只是虚拟数据，您可以
get your data from anything for which
从任何可以获取数据的地方
there's an item reader of which that
有一个项目阅读器
list is a long list so you can see neo4j
此列表很长，因此您可以看到neo4j
and hibernate j BCE and json-ld if' and
并休眠j BCE和json-ld if'和
lists and Mongo and repositories and XML
列表，Mongo，存储库和XML
and files and stored procedures and all
和文件，存储过程以及所有
these kinds of things and and so that's
这些事情，所以这是
fine right we don't need to worry about
很好的权利，我们不必担心
that but I'm gonna just synthesize some
那，但我要合成一些
dummy data here and the ID will be
此处为虚拟数据，ID为
increment and get actually better yet
增加并实际上变得更好
we're going to say if I eat up increment
我们要说的是我是否吃光了增量
and get less than 10,000 then we want to
并获得少于10,000，那么我们想要
get the window cut into a customer and I
把窗户切成客户，我
will say if math.random is greater than
会说math.random是否大于
0.5 gain otherwise was a ok there we go
0.5增益，否则就可以了
and find me in where we turn null so
并在我们变成零的地方找到我
null means the end of the batch so again
null表示批次结束，因此再次
this is great for like if you imagine
如果您想像，这非常适合
you have a job that writes things to a
您有一份将内容写到
kafka queue our topic rather and
卡夫卡宁愿我们的话题排队
something comes along in the evening or
晚上有东西出现
whatever every hour and then just
不管每小时，然后
consumes everything from that queue that
消耗了该队列中的所有内容
that topic and then does some processing
该主题，然后进行一些处理
it writes it to a CSV file it writes it
它将其写入CSV文件
to a database any you know standard ETL
任何您知道的标准ETL到数据库
or in this case you're you're taking
或者在这种情况下，您正在
data from a streaming system and you're
来自流式传输系统的数据
moving it into persistence archival
将其纳入持久性档案
right you want to store it in a database
想要将其存储在数据库中
no or something like that spring batch
否或类似的春季批
is perfect for that because now you know
对此非常完美，因为现在您知道
you can you can tap whatever data is
你可以点击任何数据
coming out of the streaming system once
从流媒体系统中出来一次
you're done with it you send it to a
完成后，将其发送到
place with a large buffer size you know
你知道缓冲区很大的地方
so that you can keep you know whatever a
这样您就可以随时知道
half an hour ten minutes five minutes
半小时十分钟五分钟
whatever worth of data then you run this
不管有多少数据，您都可以运行
job right every whatever and it'll start
随便什么工作都会开始
pulling down data and and then you know
提取数据，然后您知道
writing it to your back-end system so
将其写入后端系统，以便
here I'm just creating a reader that
在这里，我只是在创建一个读者
will just keep producing new records
只会继续产生新记录
until I have 10,000 records okay once
直到我有10,000条记录
it's done it'll send null let it return
完成后，将发送null使其返回
null and that tells spring batch to stop
null，这告诉Spring Batch停止
trying to read and it's gonna read by
试图阅读，它将被阅读
the way one it's gonna keep reading
一种继续阅读的方式
it'll keep calling weed until it reaches
它会一直叫杂草直到达到
this chunk size at which point it
这个块的大小
accumulate all those read items into a
将所有读取的项目累积到一个
container a collection and ship it to
容器收集并运送到
the writer and the writer is the Kafka
作家，作家是卡夫卡
idle writer so that chunk size that you
闲置的编写器，以便您使用块大小
saw me specify in the job step down here
看到我在这里下达工作
ten it's gonna do that a thousand times
十将做一千遍
basically it's going to accumulate ten
基本上会累积十
at a time into memory and then write all
一次写入内存，然后全部写入
ten to the Kafka item writer which is
十个给卡夫卡项目作家
going to try and do it in a larger
打算尝试做一个更大的
person trying to
试图去的人
you know as fast as possible if not an
如果不是的话，您会尽快知道
actual transaction so if using JDBC
实际事务，因此，如果使用JDBC
that's an actual transaction it'll
这是实际的交易
actually put everything in one logical
实际上把一切合乎逻辑
transaction and if something fails in
交易，如果失败
writing any one of those ten records at
将这十个记录中的任何一个写在
a rollback called ten okay so let's see
回滚称为十行，所以让我们来看看
that looks normal
看起来很正常
good don't need that there's our there's
好，不需要，有我们的，有
our code that's a program that will
我们的代码是一个程序
write data and so what I'm gonna do is
写数据，所以我要做的是
I'm gonna set the Kafka cop cat here
我要把卡夫卡警察猫放在这里
okay so we want Kafka cat and topic will
好吧，所以我们要卡夫卡猫和主题
be customers and what else does it need
成为客户，还有什么需要
it needs the broker - be localhost 9090
它需要经纪人-是本地主机9090
- okay so there's the data that we had
-好的，所以我们有数据
before is there I'm gonna do what I'm
之前我要去做我所要做的
gonna do I'm gonna just restart
我要重新开始
everything
一切
I'll just reset my Kafka set up by using
我将使用重置我的Kafka设置
I'm using confluence desktop thing and
我正在使用融合桌面的东西，
it solves everything nice and easy so I
它可以解决所有问题，所以我
don't have to worry about it so let me
不用担心，让我
see source okay good stuff okay
看到源好东西好
so I've just reset everything I've got
所以我只重设所有东西
no car you know I just reinstalled
没有车，你知道我刚刚重新安装
everything you know from nothing and now
你从无到有现在所知道的一切
you can see that this doesn't exist
您可以看到这不存在
there's no data there there's nothing
没有数据就没有
right so I now need to run this program
对，所以我现在需要运行该程序
and that'll actually initialize my my
这实际上会初始化我的
destination so here's my producer let's
目的地，所以这是我的制片人
run it
运行
okay so the program ran didn't take very
好吧，所以程序运行起来并不需要
long at all even with my CPU being
即使我的CPU也很长
pegged as a QuickTime recording and so
固定为QuickTime录音等等
if I go here you can see I've got you
如果我去这里，你会看到我得到你
know all the data that I thought I
知道我以为我的所有数据
should have okay so there's that that's
应该可以的，那就是
good now now what we have we have all
现在好现在我们拥有的一切
the data in the in the in the Kafka
卡夫卡中的数据
queue and now I want to read it don't I
排队，现在我想阅读，不是吗
so I want to go now and create a
所以我现在想去创建一个
consumer application so here it is here
消费者应用程序，所以在这里
consumer Kafka consumer you know
您知道的卡夫卡消费者
consumer application here we're gonna do
我们将在这里进行消费者应用程序
the same thing in Reverse we're gonna
反向中同样的事情
read the data that's been written to the
读取已写入的数据
database or in this case to Kafka so
数据库或在这种情况下到Kafka这样
Springwood application and by the way
Springwood的应用方式
like a very common thing is to use
就像一个很普通的事情是使用
spring match and spring integration
春季比赛和春季比赛
together so maybe you are using spring
在一起，所以也许你正在使用弹簧
intubation and you're doing messaging
插管，您正在进行消息传递
and that's the thing that's producing
这就是正在产生的东西
the data right and you're so you get a
数据正确，您就可以
channel that has data in it
里面有数据的通道
there's something called a job launching
有一种叫做工作启动的东西
message Handler and that comes from the
消息处理程序，它来自
spring batch integration project and
春季批次整合项目和
what that does is it it does exactly
那是什么呢？
that you send a message to the job
您向该职位发送消息
launching message header telling it what
启动消息标题告诉它什么
job you want to launch and what
您要启动的工作以及什么
parameters you want to use and as a
您要使用的参数以及
result of a message coming in on a
一条消息的结果
channel it'll kick off a spring batch
渠道将启动春季批
job by default the way we're using it
默认情况下，我们使用它的方式
right now when you run the spring boot
现在，当您运行spring boot时
program it automatically launches any
程序自动启动任何
spring batch jobs that are in the
春季批处理作业
application context but if you want to
应用程序上下文，但是如果您想
run a job as a result of some sort of
由于某种原因而工作
processing pipeline maybe you see a file
处理管道，也许您会看到一个文件
or something like that you can say oh I
或类似的东西，你可以说哦，我
here's a inbound file adapter in spring
这是春天的入站文件适配器
aggregation prompts that notice notice
聚合提示通知通知
is a new file and in some sort of mount
是一个新文件并且以某种形式挂载
or something you know and then that
或你知道的东西，然后
kicks off the job which does the ETL
开始执行ETL的工作
which then writes that data to Kafka
然后将数据写入Kafka
right or or you know whatever and then
对或者你知道什么然后
if it writes it to Kafka that can
如果将其写入Kafka可以
trigger some sort of streaming
触发某种流
processing pipeline which then has an
处理管道，然后有一个
put which then needs to be loaded back
放，然后需要装回
into the database and that's where
进入数据库，那就是
spring batch can help you again as a
春季批可以再次帮助您
REIT as a listener as a consumer that's
REIT作为倾听者和消费者
what we're going to look at right here
我们在这里要看的东西
so let's do that we need the same kind
所以我们需要相同的种类
of basic setup as the first time right
基本设置的第一次
we've got the a table spring batch okay
我们有一个桌子弹簧批次好
our batch processing I suppose good
我想我们的批处理很好
public static void mean already okay dot
公共静态无效意味着已经可以了
run consumer application dot class cool
运行消费者应用程序点类很酷
and what do we want to do well we want
我们想要做的好
to have a job okay so in order to create
做好工作，以便创建
the job we need this job lunch or
我们需要这份工作午餐
factory and the step sorry the job
工厂和步骤对不起工作
builder Factory and the step builder
建造者工厂和步骤建造者
Factory so same as before
工厂和以前一样
builder factory okay same thing as
建造者工厂好吗
before I'm gonna inject that into the
在我将其注入到
constructor I'll say required arts
建设者，我会说必修课
constructor that I'll create a
我将创建一个构造函数
constructor that has parameters and
具有参数和的构造函数
storage for these fields it'll
这些字段的存储
automatically initialize them doing it
自动初始化他们这样做
exactly what I would do if I hit alt
如果我按下alt，该怎么办
enter just generate the constructor and
输入只是生成构造函数，
once I have the job what do I want to do
一旦我有了工作，我想做什么
want to say job builder Factory dot get
想说工作建立者工厂点得到
job whatever
工作随便
implementer new NID incrementer start
实施者新的NID增量器启动
build right we need a step so come back
建立正确，我们需要一步，所以回来
to this in a second goody
第二个礼物
okay and our step is you know again
好吧，我们的步骤是您再次知道
we're going to read data so nothing
我们将要读取数据，所以什么也没有
particularly fancy here it's gonna be
特别喜欢这里
using the step filter Factory
使用步进滤波器工厂
you should give them more descriptive
你应该给他们更多的描述性
names because remember it's this gets
之所以命名，是因为记住了
persistent to the database it's how we
持久到数据库，这就是我们的方式
can look up the state of this particular
可以查询此特定状态
step later on so don't do as I'm doing
以后再做，所以不要像我一样做
do better I know you can so we're again
做得更好，我知道你可以，所以我们再次
we're gonna read it here so the chunk
我们要在这里阅读，所以大块
really is what are we gonna write to in
真的是我们要写的东西
this case I'm gonna write to the console
这种情况下我要写到控制台
I'm just gonna write a I'm gonna plug in
我要写一个我要插入
a dummy item writer that would just log
一个虚拟物品作家，只会记录
all the data nothing interesting here so
所有的数据都没什么有趣的，所以
it doesn't really matter what the chunk
到底什么块并不重要
size is there's no risk of there's a
大小是没有风险的
risk of like being overwhelmed just uh
就像不堪重负的危险
no real risk really you know I'm just
没有真正的风险，真的，你知道我只是
gonna logs to him but you should you
要登录到他，但你应该
should definitely take more care when
绝对应该多加注意
you said this than I have cuz I don't
你说的比我说的要多
really need to I'm not writing saving a
真的需要我不写保存
moment that's a good point you can use
那一刻你可以使用的好点
Kafka as a way to stage as a way to
卡夫卡作为登台的一种方式
absorb writes so Cochran can take it if
吸收写作，所以科克伦可以接受
you're not sure if you if you have a lot
你不确定是否有很多
of data that needs to be written into a
需要写入的数据
sequel data store like Oracle or
后续数据存储，例如Oracle或
something that don't drop you know you
不会掉的东西你知道你
can't drop the same unit amount of data
不能删除相同数量的数据
on an Oracle database you can't write to
在您无法写入的Oracle数据库上
an Oracle Oracle database even if you
Oracle Oracle数据库，即使您
drop all the indexes and all that stuff
删除所有索引和所有东西
you're just not gonna be able to write
你只是不会写
as fast as you can to a Kafka so this
尽快到Kafka，所以这
might be exactly the kind of thingy
可能恰好是那种东西
which is you have something that can
你有什么可以
drain the queue and then attempt to
排空队列，然后尝试
write to the Oracle database slowly and
慢慢写入Oracle数据库，然后
you can do things with spring batch you
你可以用春季批处理来做你
can actually you know do remote chunking
你实际上知道远程分块吗
where you actually have it spin off
你实际上在哪里分拆
where it actually fans out to work or
它实际上散布在哪里工作或
nodes on a cluster and then it pulls in
群集上的节点，然后拉入
data from the the Kafka you know you
您知道的来自Kafka的数据
could I can imagine it you know pulling
我能想象你知道拉吗
data down from a different topic or
来自不同主题的数据或
different partitions in Kafka on each
卡夫卡上每个分区的不同分区
node for example
例如节点
you know a lots of things lots of
你知道很多事情
opportunities built into spring batches
春季批次中的机会
of framework itself and that those only
框架本身
get better with them with with Kafka
与Kafka一起使他们变得更好
which is built for scale as well so okay
这也是为了规模而建立的
step build a factory writer is gonna
一步建立工厂作家将
plug that in as head of our writer new
作为我们作家的负责人插入
item writer customer okay alright and
项目编写者客户还可以，
I'm gonna use a logger when you use
当您使用时，我将使用记录器
log4j okay log this out I want to do
log4j好的，注销我要执行的操作
that for each item it in the collections
对于收藏中的每个项目
of items so I'm going to say items up
的项目，所以我要说的项目
for each
每个
okay how about that and all right so
好的，那好吧
there's that and the real magic here the
那就是这里真正的魔力
thing I want to show on this side is of
我想在这边展示的是
course the reader that's the Kafka
当然是卡夫卡的读者
reader slowly say reader okay and did we
读者慢慢说，读者好吗，我们
provide the beam already nope okay let's
提供光束已经不行了，让我们
do that here so I've been kaka item
在这里做，所以我一直是卡卡项目
reader simple right right okay so first
读者简单，对，对，好吧，首先
things first we need a new Kafka item
首先，我们需要一个新的卡夫卡物品
reader builder and it'll be dice a
读者生成器，这将是一个骰子
string it's a long isn't it so it's a
字符串很长，不是吗？
long and a customer
长和一个客户
so what partitions well I'm just gonna
那我要分区什么
use one leg out the one at this point we
在这一点上，我们用一只脚
need some consumer properties and this
需要一些消费者属性，这
is where you know we get some help with
您知道我们可以从中获得一些帮助的地方
the auto configuration here bar props
这里的自动配置栏道具
equals u properties ok and what I need
等于您的属性还可以，我需要什么
is the consumer properties from the add
是添加的消费者属性
up for the property file the application
为属性文件申请
up properties it's all inject the
的属性都注入
cough-cough properties object which is
咳嗽特性的对象
behind the scenes here it's kind of a
在幕后，这有点像
thing that gets leaked from iam the auto
从iam auto泄漏的东西
configuration but I do need it so I'll
配置，但我确实需要它，所以我会
use that so properties props that put
使用该属性道具
all this properties dot what I want
所有这些属性点了我想要的
those consumer properties I guess this
那些消费者属性我猜这
looks right okay
看起来还好吧
and give it a name it's gonna call
给它起个名字
customers waiter
客户服务员
sure and build and don't want to save
确定并建立，不想保存
state you bet chide you okay oh and we
声明你敢责骂你好吧哦，我们
need to topic tell me we need to tell it
需要话题告诉我，我们需要告诉它
we need to tell it where to read from
我们需要告诉它从哪里读取
right so topic will be customers that's
对，因此主题将是
what we said right in the property file
我们在属性文件中说的正确
so I can probably have injected that too
所以我也可以注入
I should probably not duplicate that but
我可能不应该重复
it's the default topic is here for the
这是默认主题
reader sorry for the writer and on the
读者为作者感到抱歉，并在
consumer side its customers here so
消费者方面在这里的客户
they're sharing the same address in the
他们在共享相同的地址
broker okay I think that's it we need to
经纪人好吧，我想就是我们需要的
plug that in Kafka item reader I got the
插入卡夫卡项目阅读器中，我得到了
writer so we know we've already got data
作家，所以我们知道我们已经有数据
in the database we already saw that
在数据库中，我们已经看到
right I I wrote a bunch of data to Kafka
右二写了一些数据给卡夫卡
it's here we needed to pull that data
在这里，我们需要提取数据
out now okay so there's all that let's
现在出去好了，所以所有的让我们
now read it using this consumer
现在使用此消费者阅读它
and there we go
然后我们去
doesn't host this topic partition well
不能很好地托管此主题分区
that doesn't seem fair is it zero I
这似乎不公平吗，我是零
should have done zero
应该做零
what kind of nerd am i that i didn't i
我不是我是哪种书呆子
didn't use zero Visual Basic nerd that's
没有使用零的Visual Basic书呆子
what kind alright alright what have I
什么样的好吧我有什么
done now
现在完成
oh it says I can't cast a string to a
哦，它说我无法将字符串转换为
so why would it do that did I screw up
那我为什么搞砸了
the property configuration here let's
这里的属性配置
see for the consumer side value - Sierra
查看消费者方面的价值-塞拉利昂
Lazard is Jason - sterilizer long long
Lazard is Jason-消毒器长久
seems legit trusted packages are correct
似乎合法的可信软件包是正确的
and I somehow
我不知何故
where does it
在哪里
hmm
嗯
right items do the right what did I have
正确的物品正确的我有什么
sort of in I mean incorrect data I've
我的意思是我有不正确的数据
got a writer
有作家
what's the writer is a issue I had a
作者是我的一个问题
reader see item writer made of
读者请参阅由
long customer long and customer
长期客户长期客户
unmodifiable collection so it's saying
不可修改的收藏所以说
that it's got the the value that it has
它具有它所具有的价值
is a value to see Eliezer on the oh I
看到埃利泽在我身上很有价值
had a properties element in there so it
那里有一个属性元素，所以它
was trying to use the default oh that's
试图使用默认值哦
so bad okay so that should work if you
太糟糕了，好了，如果您
can't come in click on it inside of the
不能点击里面的
IDE it's it's I'm using the properties
IDE是因为我正在使用属性
element which is just a map of arbitrary
只是任意图的元素
keys and values it's just it doesn't
键和值只是它不是
mean anything so it was trying to use
什么意思，所以它试图使用
the default no wonder it was so upset
默认，难怪它是如此难过
okay so there we go
好的，所以我们去了
look at that when I fix that it now
当我现在修复它时看看
knows about the right DC Eliezer and
了解正确的DC Eliezer，
there's all my data and that my friend
有我所有的数据，还有我的朋友
has been a very quick look very quick
看起来非常快
look at using Kafka and spring batch and
看看使用Kafka和spring batch和
again the real opportunity here is it's
再次，真正的机会是
in the innovation it's in the possible
在创新中有可能
integrations the streaming to badge and
将流媒体集成到徽章和
batches of streaming use cases imagine
成批的流用例想象
taking data off of a message queue and
从消息队列中取出数据，以及
then writing into some sort of
然后写成某种
persistent store or archiving in or
永久存储或归档在或
whatever putting it in a warehouse for
不管把它放在仓库里
analytics this is the exactly the kind
分析，这正是那种
of glue code that you need to write to
您需要写入的胶水代码
get that kind of work done and it could
完成这样的工作，它可以
be also the place where you do the
也是你做的地方
processing in of itself right so spring
本身就是春天
batch is great for this kind of stuff
批处理非常适合这种东西
all in all I'm super excited to see this
总而言之，我很高兴看到这个
land and spring back I hope you'll give
土地和春天回来，我希望你能给
it a shot and feedback obviously we're
一枪和反馈显然我们
not yet g8 so the sooner the better
尚未g8，所以越早越好
alright thanks so much for watching and
好，非常感谢您的收看和
again we'll see you next
下次我们再见
you
您